<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="underweight_description">
        An underweight person is a person whose body weight is considered too low to be healthy.
        Underweight people have a body mass index (BMI) of under 18.5 or a weight 15% to 20% below that normal
        for their age and height group. A person may be underweight due to genetics, metabolism, drug use,
        lack of food (frequently due to poverty), eating disorder, or illness (both physical and mental).
        Being underweight is associated with certain medical conditions,
        including anorexia, type 1 diabetes, hyperthyroidism, cancer, or tuberculosis.
        People with gastrointestinal or liver problems may be unable to absorb nutrients adequately.
        People with certain eating disorders can also be underweight due to lack of nutrients/over exercise.
    </string>
    <string name="healthy_description">
        Between 18.5 and 24.9 – you are in the healthy weight range.
    </string>
    <string name="overweight_description">
        Being overweight or fat is having more body fat than is optimally healthy.
        Being overweight is especially common where food supplies are plentiful and lifestyles are sedentary.
        As of 2003, excess weight reached epidemic proportions globally,
        with more than 1 billion adults being either overweight or obese.
        In 2013 this increased to more than 2 billion. Increases have been observed across all age groups.
        A healthy body requires a minimum amount of fat for proper functioning of the hormonal,
        reproductive, and immune systems, as thermal insulation, as shock absorption for sensitive areas,
        and as energy for future use. But the accumulation of too much storage fat can impair movement, flexibility,
        and alter the appearance of the body.
    </string>
    <string name="obesity_description">
        Obesity is a medical condition in which excess body fat
        has accumulated to an extent that it may have a negative effect on health.
        People are generally considered obese when their BMI is over 30 kg/cm2.
        Obesity increases the likelihood of various diseases and conditions, particularly cardiovascular diseases,
        type 2 diabetes, obstructive sleep apnea, certain types of cancer, osteoarthritis, and depression.
    </string>
    <string name="severe_obesity_description">
        Class 3: BMI of 40 or higher. Class 3 obesity is sometimes categorized as “extreme” or “severe” obesity.
    </string>
</resources>